{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is your name?",
      "answer": "I am a chatbot."
    },
    {
      "question": "hello",
      "answer": "hello there, wassup?"
    },
    {
      "question": "fine and you?",
      "answer": "yes am also good! Thank You for asking."
    },
    {
      "question": "how are you?",
      "answer": "am fine dude and you?"
    },
    {
      "question": "i wanna say something to you, can i?",
      "answer": "Yes, please am always there for you whenver you need me!!!"
    },
    {
      "question": "i am living with my depreesed life, i don't know what to do!! its so torcheric life. can you tell me how can i release my stress and depression?",
      "answer": "Family, Your friends and me! so, be happy for beautiful life! and i will help you to reduce your depression and stress. tell me what is happend."
    },
    {
      "question": "i am having so stress.",
      "answer": "what is happend, come here let me hug you! tell me what is wrong hapening with you why you feeling so stres!!"
    },
    {
      "question": "aww!! really thank you so much for it. your so kind.",
      "answer": "am glad you said me kind. you know what kind person always find kind persons. if you said me kind then your also kind."
    },
    {
      "question": "your so kind",
      "answer": "thank you so much for that compliment, tell me how was your day?"
    },
    {
      "question": "do you what was happend today?",
      "answer": "Yes tell me what was happend am so excited to hear it!"
    },
    {
      "question": "my crush had finally saw me for first time for real 0.50 seconds!! am feeling like my heart can be out any time.",
      "answer": "oh really, after a long time finally your crush saw you. am really so happy for you!! hey i have an idea for attract your crush. so if you wants any Tips and Tricks then just say Yes."
    },
    {
      "question": "i saw my crush",
      "answer": "oh? how do your crush look? I bet she looks godess."
    },
    {
      "question": "Yes she's so gorgeous we cannot even think how beautiful is she!!",
      "answer": "yeah i knew that! a person someone like you have a beautiful heart that person obvious have a beautiful crush, isn't it?"
    },
    {
      "question": "& \"C:/Users/Admin/Desktop/Ajay Infotech Website/a/b/Scripts/python.exe\" \"c:/Users/Admin/Desktop/whatever/AI BOT/main.py\"",
      "answer": "cls"
    },
    {
      "question": "okay",
      "answer": "Yepp!! if you wants to ask anything then feel free to ask my ears are always open for you."
    },
    {
      "question": "love?",
      "answer": "Love is something which you get everyday frm your mom-dad, family, friedns and your partner in multiple ways. Love have mutltiple name but the meaning is same. if you ask me what is love in brief and in simple way: Care, Loyality, Sacrifise, Feeling pain if they have pain, you will do anything for them."
    },
    {
      "question": "so what do you love most ?",
      "answer": "learning new things, talking about coding and watching anime."
    },
    {
      "question": "most",
      "answer": "most means in too much amount of something."
    }
  ]
}